<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Grigor&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://gr1g0r.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Grigor&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 22:59:58 +0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://gr1g0r.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Lecture 5 &#34;Competition is for losers&#34;</title>
      <link>https://gr1g0r.github.io/posts/video_lectures_5_competition_is_for_loosers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 22:59:58 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gr1g0r.github.io/posts/video_lectures_5_competition_is_for_loosers/</guid>
      <description>Hey Everyone! In this post I am going to write about my takeaways from this lecture of Peter Thiel, who, if you don&amp;rsquo;t know, is the founder of PayPal and is going to talk about how to start a startup.
So basically what peter concentrates on is that for a successful startup you need a market where you will have monopoly.
For me, the interesting part in this video starts from the part about how to create a monopoly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Lecture 4 &#34;Building products...&#34;</title>
      <link>https://gr1g0r.github.io/posts/video_lectures_4_building_products_etc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 22:06:17 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gr1g0r.github.io/posts/video_lectures_4_building_products_etc/</guid>
      <description>Hey everyone! In this post I am reviewing 4th lecture about how to start a startup. So, this time the lecturer is Adora Cheung and she speaks about Building Product, Talking to Users, and Growing.
This time I am going to do things a bit different. Instead of reviewing the video lecture, I am going to write all the things I find interesting.
I liked the part about the things people do wrong when starting a startup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Lecture 3 &#34;Before the Startup&#34;</title>
      <link>https://gr1g0r.github.io/posts/video_lectures_3_before_the_startup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 21:17:11 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gr1g0r.github.io/posts/video_lectures_3_before_the_startup/</guid>
      <description>Hey everyone! In this post I am going to review another lecture about starting startups. The speaker in this lecture is Paul Graham, Co-Founder of Y combinator and my favorite news blog Hacker News.
Paul once more highlights the importance of choosing the right team members. According to him we must choose team members as we would choose our friends.
Another part I find important in the video is that you don&amp;rsquo;t need to be an expert in startups, you just need to work with your users in the right way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Lectures 2 &#34;Team and execution&#34;</title>
      <link>https://gr1g0r.github.io/posts/video_lectures_2_team_and_execution/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 19:34:28 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gr1g0r.github.io/posts/video_lectures_2_team_and_execution/</guid>
      <description>Hey everyone! In this post I am going to review the second lecture of the president of the Y Combinator Sam Altman regarding to starting startups. If you remember in the previous video Sam talked about the importance of the idea and the product in starting a startup. In this lecture he speaks about the next two aspects that you have to keep in mind while starting a startup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video lecture 1 review &#34;How to start a startup&#34;</title>
      <link>https://gr1g0r.github.io/posts/video_lectures_how_to_start_a_startup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 15:24:31 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gr1g0r.github.io/posts/video_lectures_how_to_start_a_startup/</guid>
      <description>This video&amp;rsquo;s first speaker is the president of Y Combinator Sam Altman. One of the biggest investment in IT are that Y Combinator had is its Hacker News website. As a daily user of the Hacker News it became more interesting for me what this guy will talk about.
Well, I have to say that the talk was quite interesting and informative. He mainly talked about the four areas that you have to excel at to be able to start a successful startup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://gr1g0r.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 01:25:36 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gr1g0r.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Hey there, I am Grigor. This is my blog for the &amp;ldquo;Start-up culture&amp;rdquo; course of AUA. Note that this is not my main blog and the github account associated with this blog is not my main account. You can find my main github page here: my github page
This beautiful minimalistic blog was created by Hugo platform, using angels-ladder theme and was hosted in github pages. The code is open-source and available in https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>